Somebody has been lying to us. I believe
that Epstein was an Israeli access
agent. If the Israelis want to recruit a
former president, a British prince,
they're not recruitable. You recruit the
guy right next [music] to them, to whom
you give millions of dollars so he can
entertain these people at his private
island where the rooms are all wired for
audio and video. You supply underage
girls. You make them your best friends.
>> There's a lot of crazy things happening
in the world.
>> Yeah. Oh.
>> Um, speaking of which, of crazy things
happening, did you did you see that the
I think it was the FBI said they're
going to release a video of Epstein
having killed himself.
>> What are your what are your thoughts on
that?
>> Well, somebody has been lying to us,
right, all along because we were told
years ago there was no video, that the
cameras were down,
>> right?
>> Right. Um, and I even went on the
record, I wrote a piece saying I didn't
believe this was a conspiracy because
having been in prison for two years
myself, I can tell you number one,
everybody has his head up his ass who's
working for the Federal Bureau of
Prisons. Literally everybody. It's It's
like they stand on the street corner in
the worst parts of town and shout, "Hey,
anybody here want to be a prison guard?"
And those are the people they hire. We
had trouble at mail call. We had trouble
at mail call because the guards couldn't
read and so they had to have the
prisoners read the mail and hand out the
the mail. Yeah. They can't read.
>> So number one, everybody's got his head
up his ass. Number two,
>> as a general rule, the cameras are
always broken or they're turned off.
Always.
>> Okay. Number three,
the guards are supposed to walk around
every 15 minutes and look in every cell
and make sure you know you're not
hanging from a sheet. They never walk
around ever. They sit in the little
guard booth surfing the internet looking
at porn, playing solitire,
whatever.
Um, and they were supposed to put uh
Epstein in with uh you know, some guy to
watch him to make him make sure that he
didn't uh do it. I've heard two things.
one that there was nobody in the cell or
two that while there was somebody in the
cell that person was an accused serial
killer.
So it's like
>> okay
>> yeah
so now they're telling us they have
video and that the video shows them
committing suicide. Okay, if you have
the video release the video. Let's see
it. I want to see if the hyoid bone was
broken by the sheet
>> or the the action of his body snapping
as he dropped or if somebody strangled
him. Show us if there's a video. What
What are we waiting for? Who Who do you
think would have been most highly
incentivized to take him out? I I know
that there's a lot of speculation around
who Epste was connected to, but from
where you're sitting, what does it look
like? I personally believe he committed
suicide
just because,
>> okay,
>> there's there's so many moving parts in
a conspiracy. It's it's they're almost
impossible to enact first and second,
even if you enact them, they're
impossible to keep quiet. So, I I
believe facing life without parole,
there's no parole in the federal system.
He knew he was never going to see the
light of day ever again. And because he
was a convicted uh pedophile,
he would never be able to serve a single
day in a minimum security work camp.
>> So he was done,
>> right?
>> He was done.
>> Um
>> yeah, he saw the writing on the wall.
>> Yeah,
>> he had no outs. But to answer your
question, I think of all the different
factions who have been either implicated
or accused of having having had some
involvement in this whole situation, I
think it was the Israelis that had the
most to gain taking him out. I I was on
a I was part of a
>> debate. Why?
>> Yeah. Why is that?
>> Well, I believe that Epstein was an
Israeli access agent.
An access agent is a very specific kind
of of recruited agent. If you Okay, I
I'll preface what is I I'll Yeah, I'll
preface it with a story to explain what
an access agent is. One of my
instructors at the CIA
told me once in training that the best
recruitment he ever had was a copy
machine repair man.
And and I laughed when he said it. He
said, "No, no, hear me out."
He said,
All of us want to recruit the prime
minister, right? None of us are going to
recruit a prime minister. Prime
Ministers aren't recruitable.
But copy machine repairmen are
recruitable.
And eventually the copy machine in the
prime minister's office is going to go
down and it's going to need to be
cleaned or repaired. And so you recruit
the repairmen and he goes into the
office of the prime minister to clean
the machine, clean the drums and install
a little device that we give him so that
every time somebody makes a photocopy,
it transmits another copy to CIA
headquarters. He said, "I got promoted.
>> Oh my gosh.
>> I got a medal. I got a photo op with the
director." He said, "It was the best
recruitment of my life."
Okay, look at Jeffrey Epstein.
If the Israelis want to recruit
a former president,
a British prince, you know, sixth in
line to the throne, the founder of
Microsoft, you're not going to recruit
any of those people. They're not
recruitable. But you recruit somebody
almost as good. You recruit the guy
right next to them. You recruit the guy
next to them
to whom you give millions of dollars
so he can entertain these people at his
private island where the rooms are all
wired for audio and video. You supply
underage girls.
You make them your best friends
and then you just turn everything over
to us and we decide what to do with it.
That's what an access agent is. And I
think that's
>> a conduit for information.
>> They're a conduit. That's right. Yeah.
Jeffrey Epstein as Jeffrey Epstein
didn't have access to classified
information, but everybody around him
did,
>> right?
>> And so that's the guy
>> did. Mhm.
>> If if you get rid of the underage girls
part, the rest of it seems so benign and
innocuous. Like, oh, we're just going to
a baseball or we're just doing whatever
we do and we're just hanging out and I'm
I'm paying for it, you know, cuz I like
you.
>> That's a good point.
>> And it is. And that's a great
observation. And and if if an operation
is that benal,
>> you're going to give that guy a thousand
bucks a month, okay? and you're going to
meet with him once a month in a coffee
shop and you're going to say, "So, what
fun gossip have you heard this month?"
And he's going to say, "Oh, Bill and
Hillary Clinton are fighting and they're
disagreeing over, you know, Trump's
budget cuts." Because who cares
if it's a Jeffrey Epstein situation?
>> You know, that reminds me,
>> it's different. It reminds me of uh if
you ever read Sherlock Holmes, that was
always Holmes's uh intel is he always
had all the homeless kids on the
streets. He would pay them all, you
know, a nickel or whatever the token was
and they would just scatter around all
of London and then they'd all report
back to him on anything that they found
cuz he's like
>> nobody pays attention to those kids. And
>> there is, you know, and they're the
they're the ones that can kind of go
anywhere and no one no one sees them as
a threat. If you want to see the full
conversation, please subscribe and check
out the link in the description. Thanks
a lot.